wishpot.com 2008-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Wishpot

**Last Revised: November 10, 2006**

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains when and how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed with respect to our web site located at www.wishpot.com (the "Site"). [By using the Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us. **We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time.Ã¡ We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the privacy policy the date it was last updated. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes or revised statement shall constitute your consent to any changes in our privacy practices.** Ã¡ Please carefully review this policy whenever you visit our Site so you understand our data privacy practices and can make an informed decision about using our Site.

## What is Personal Information?

As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or other account number), and information about that individual's activities, such as information about his or her use of the Site, when directly linked to personally identifiable information. Ã¡Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about the use of the Site or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Site. Ã¡This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

## Personal Information We Collect 

We collect personal information in a number of ways when you visit our Site. At several places on our Site, we may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information.Ã¡ For example, we collect personal information, such as your name, address, photograph and other contact and demographic information when you: (1) register and set up an account; (2) sign up for any of our e-mail newsletters; (3) post an entry  or (4) contact us by e-mail for any reason. Ã¡Personal information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with creating a profile, leaving comments, providing a review, inviting a friend, sending an email or message to another user or participating in any interactive forums or features on the site.Ã¡ In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Site.

When you visit our web site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit and purchases. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only. Ã¡We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies."Ã¡ For more information on how we use cookies and other information that we automatically collect, please see the section below entitled "Cookies, IP Addresses and URLs"

## How We Use Personal Information

In general, we use personal information we collect to process your requests or transactions, Ã¡to provide you with information, products or services you request, and to facilitate your use of the Site and our administration and operation of the Site.Ã¡ We may also use personal information for our internal marketing such as Ã¡to inform you about other products, services, events, information, and promotions we think will be of interest. For example, we may use the information we collection:

lto send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Site, such as for administrative purposes or to provide you with customer service;

lto provide you with the services, products or information you requested and to complete any transactions in connection therewith;

lto respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;

lto request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications, products and services;

lto contact you about our services, products, training, activities or special events or offers and for other internal marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes;

lto notify contest winners; and

for the specific purpose for which the information was provided.

Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our partners. In addition, if we receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In either case, this Policy governs this information.

## Public Postings, Content and Ratings

You can publish a wish list on the Site as well as publishing various , comments, reviews and other content on various portions of the Site . Members can choose to rate products, services or other wishes, and to connect to other members. As an unregistered visitor, we do not allow you to rate products and/or reviews or to enter comments.

Certain information that you post on the Site may be displayed publicly and shared with other users, I such as items on your wish list, reviews, comments, and your user profile.Ã¡ Your use of the Site constitutes your consent to share this information publicly.Ã¡ You may elect to restrict access to certain information, such as your profile and wish list, by using the available privacy settings.Ã¡ Please be aware, however, that although we use commercially reasonable efforts to implement these restrictions and honor these designations, no system or security measure is perfect or impenetrable, and therefore, we cannot guarantee that this information will not be available to others.Ã¡ You should also be aware that regardless of the setting you select for your own wish list and profile, personal information that you post in connection with other user's wish lists or in any comments, reviews, profile, discussion groups, email, or any other interactive areas of the Site that are not designated as private, or other information that is provided for the purpose of being shared is publicly available and can potentially be viewed by anyone.Ã¡ In addition, your member name is automatically displayed with wishes and comments you publish, and if other members choose to, they can receive email notifications of your publications or publish their own comments to your items.

We publish product ratings and use them to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views and merchandise products. We use your items, comments and reviews to personalize the site and identify/feature popular members. For example, we may promote most popular items and members. While we don't expect to transfer the complete review and member database to others (except as contemplated elsewhere in this statement), we use the database throughout our networks and to generate results for others.

## Security

We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. We have put in place email notifications to let you know of any changes to your account.Ã¡ To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our web site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.

## Control of Personal Information

We give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us and to view, correct or delete your personal information.

  1. If you do not want to receive marketing or reminder e-mail from us, or emails notifying you when comments have been posted to your wish list, you can; (a) click on "Account" and alter your preferences accordingly; or (b) follow the opt-out instructions at the bottom of any email you receive from us.
  2. If you want to view, correct or delete your personal information, you can access your information online by clicking the "Account" link.
  3. For other requests or to contact us directly, see Comments or Concerns below.

## Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy (and in any updates to this policy that may be posted to the Site from time to time). Ã¡However, we may share aggregate information to third parties without your authorization.Ã¡ We may share personal information with third-party vendors, consultants and service providers ("Service Providers") who assist us in performing functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, without limitation, Website hosting. We endeavor to limit the information shared with such Service Providers to that which we believe is necessary or useful to carry out those functions. __ We are not responsible for any failure on the part of our Service Providers to comply with our privacy practices, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these Service Providers or to other third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

When you participate in the Site, certain information you post on or through the Site may be shared with other users or posted on publicly available portions of the Site, and your use of the Site constitutes your consent to share this information in such manner.Ã¡ For more information on how certain information you post on or through the Site may be shared with others or be publicly available, please see the Section above on Public Postings, Content and Ratings **.Ã¡** Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information when posting reviews, comments or other information or content to the Site, this information may be made publicly available and may be collected and used by others. You agree that we shall bear no responsibility for any such disclosures whether by Wishpot or any third party. We recommend you be cautious in giving out personal information to others in public online forums.

In addition, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Wishpot, our users, our employees or the public, including without limitation to protect Wishpot or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate or unlawful use of our Site. Information about our users, including personal information, may also be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of Wishpot.

## Cookies, IP Addresses and URLs

  1. **Automatically Collected Information:** We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. Information may be automatically collected through the use of "cookies" which are discussed in more detail below. We also collect various types of "clickstream" information which is information about your browsing behavior, such as IP address information, entry and exit points for the Site, search terms, Web site addresses you visit, page views, and impressions.
  2. **Cookies:** Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a web site when you visit. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve our sites by seeing which areas and features are most popular; to personalize the site, to improve the site experience and to complete transactions you have requested. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of our site available to the general public but you may not be able to use some of the site's features or services and you may have a less satisfactory experience. Ã¡We may use third parties to serve ads on the Site, and these third parties may place cookies or other devices on your computer to collect nonpersonal information.Ã¡ Information provided by these devices may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Sites and the other sites tracked by these third parties.Ã¡ We are not responsible for and do not control any actions or policies of any third party advertisers or advertising technology service providers.

## Use of our Web Site by Children Under 13

This Site is not intended for use by children under 13, and we do not intend to collect any personal information from children who are under 13 years of age, except as may be permitted by law. Ã¡Wish lists for children under 13 are solely intended to be created on their behalf by a parents, guardian or other user 13 years of age or over, and no personal information regarding such child should be submitted directly by a child under 13.Ã¡ If children under 13 wish to create a wish list, they should ask their parent or guardian to open an account and create one on their behalf. If you are under 13, do not attempt to create an Wishpot account and do not provide any personal information on our web site.

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our web site contains links to other web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of web sites to which we link. Links from our web site to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

## Your Comments or Concerns

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this privacy policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach us at [privacy@wishpot.com](mailto:privacy@wishpot.com), or by mail at Wishpot Inc., 1114 2nd Ave N, Seattle, WA 98109.

## Data Changes

If you terminate your account or delete/change your data or content, we usually update our live databases immediately. However, some data may update more slowly, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to propagate changes to partners who receive your data or content. If your account is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration.
